# **Eric Madsen**

Email: <a href="mailto:superspades@gmail.com">superspades@gmail.com</a>

### Languages

- Java
- C#
- SQL
- HTML / CSS
- JavaScript

## **Applications**

- Microsoft Office Suite
- Eclipse
- Visual Studio
- SQL Server Management Studio
- Oracle Developer
- Android Studio
- IBM AS400
- Red Prairie Inventory Management
- CA Erwin

#### **Skills**

- Database Design
- Software Testing
- Website Design

## **Summary**

Extensive process management experience from 17 years of warehouse employment. Worked full time while attending school until final 3 semesters. Look forward to applying the skills gained through education and previous work experience to new opportunities in programming and database management.

## **Education**

Georgia Southern University | 1332 Southern Dr. Statesboro, GA 30458 Bachelor of Science Computer Science | May 2017

■ GPA 3.35

■ 3 years Dean's List

Member ACM

## **Experience**

DOT Foods Inc. | 1120 W North St Vidalia GA 30474 | 912.538.8885

**Inventory Control | January 2014 – February 27 2016 | Supervisor: Tony Meadows** Created process to improve lot date entry accuracy and reduce processing time for production and inventory personnel.

Warehouse Support | February 2006 – January 2014 | Supervisor: Tony Meadows
Developed training program for new warehouse clerks, researched and reported production service levels, participated on Siliker quality audit team, managed RF computer inventory and repairs.

Warehouse Clerk | January 1998 – February 2006 | Supervisor: George Garbutt Trained employees at other locations on new company systems, participated in developing processes to reduce paperwork and labor time in warehouse office.

## **Projects**

Warehouse Sales Database System | April 2016 | Database Systems Course

Five-member team created a database system with GUI to simulate product ordering and sales of goods. Used CA Erwin to build relational tables and populated tables with test values using Oracle Developer, provided documentation of table properties and contents for reference in building GUI.

#### Boys and Girls Club of Vidalia Georgia | 2014 - 2015 | Computer Network Setup

Volunteered time at the Boys and Girls club to install donated computers and set up networking for use by the children. Returned on several occasions to maintain the computers and teach staff members basic management use of the systems.

#### www.superspades.com

for more information and examples of work